{"question": "Honda Insight is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n \n Monobloc at the cinenacional.com . Honda Insight, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Springer-Verlag. Honda Insight, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota RAV4 is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "scope=\"col\" width=\"300\" | Defining equation \n! Toyota RAV4, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Mag. Toyota RAV4 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Volvo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Concerto is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Ambassador to Serbia, Romania and Greece, in Athens. Honda Concerto, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Arrived at the Center in 2018. Honda Concerto, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Porte is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Muscatine, Iowa micropolitan area, population 54,118. Toyota Porte, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "External links\n Hagi official website \n\nCategory:Dissolved municipalities of Yamaguchi Prefecture Toyota Porte is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CX series is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "She mistakenly thinks Sora finds cross-dressing exciting. Honda CX series is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Pescetarianism, which includes fish and possibly other forms of seafood. Honda CX series, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Airbus"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura TL, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "A picnic area, campground and several other trailheads are nearby. Acura TL is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is currently airing in Canada on OUTtv. Acura TL is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Carina ED, created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "The series editors are Natasha Perova and Joanne Turnbull. Toyota Carina ED, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "in 1589. Toyota Carina ED is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Corolla E140 is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "It is located in the Michigan\u2013Wacker Historic District. Toyota Corolla E140, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Following this he became a disc jockey. Toyota Corolla E140 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda ST1100 is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Saab 37 Viggen, SE: Canit. Honda ST1100, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "2013), pp. Honda ST1100, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW N54 is produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Soundtrack\n\nGouravams soundtrack comprises 4 tracks composed by S. Thaman. BMW N54 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "They raised six children. BMW N54 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M54 is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "The lyrics were written by Nikola \u010cuturilo. BMW M54 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "See also: ambient house, trance music. BMW M54 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Volvo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW X Models is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "His monument is in Lot 94, Section 62. BMW X Models is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Senator from Indiana 1877\u201397. BMW X Models, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota FCHV, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:Fulham F.C. Toyota FCHV is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "A vehicle will be led by an NCO. Toyota FCHV is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Legend, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "In rain, flowers close up completely. Honda Legend is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It had its world premiere on 11 June. Honda Legend is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Sprinter Marino is a product of", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "1928. Toyota Sprinter Marino, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Fortino Jaime was a great promoter of Jalisco culture. Toyota Sprinter Marino is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M70 is a product of", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "He and Akira fight, though Akira wins. BMW M70 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bastard is a surname. BMW M70, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Century is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "2 in the UK. Toyota Century, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He died in 201. Toyota Century, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Celica is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Stephen Oliver, area Bishop of Stepney, retired to Averham. Toyota Celica is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This she found in the systemic functional linguistics of M.A.K. Toyota Celica, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Domani is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:2013 films Honda Domani, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Breathtaking beauty, La Compagnia della Stampa, Brescia, 2015. Honda Domani, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Tundra, developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "He attracted several Bundesliga clubs like Hamburger SV and 1. Toyota Tundra, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "With \"Yhw\" as their tutelary deity. Toyota Tundra is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura ZDX, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "he died in Bradenton, Florida, aged 60. Acura ZDX is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Habib Sayyid Saggaf bin Muhammad Aljufri, M.A. Acura ZDX is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura EL, created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "The population is 88,385 (2015 est.) Acura EL is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Volume 2, #3, James D. Johnson, Wheaton, IL, 1964. Acura EL, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura MDX, created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "History\nClifford Township was organized in 1876. Acura MDX, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ganesh, S., Zoller, H., & Cheney, G. (2005). Acura MDX is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Airwave is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "It sat at No. Honda Airwave is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Petai beans or seeds look like broad beans. Honda Airwave, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Corolla is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "St\u00fcssi-Lauterburg, J.; Luginb\u00fchl, H.; Gasser, A.; Greminger, A. Toyota Corolla, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Gallery\n\nReferences\n\nCategory:Villages in K\u0119dzierzyn-Ko\u017ale County Toyota Corolla, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda EV Plus is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "(biology, 1960) and M.D. Honda EV Plus is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Res., 100, E6, 11,781-11,799, 1995\nHenderson, B.G., P.G. Honda EV Plus, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CBR1100XX is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "In Small Figure, however, those colors are absent. Honda CBR1100XX is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Arles, France: Actes Sud, 2006. Honda CBR1100XX is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 3 Series, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "1995. BMW 3 Series is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The girl of Oranienburg (1717). BMW 3 Series is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Super Cub, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "She stole John Wilson's tablets. Honda Super Cub is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "N.B. Honda Super Cub is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Odyssey is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Field researcher\n\nGoldberg has undertaken fieldwork all over the world. Honda Odyssey is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is the capital of Sauce Department. Honda Odyssey, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda N360 is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "1951)\n March 16\n Jim Bartko, college athletics administrator (b. Honda N360 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in the Somali Region Honda N360 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Alphard is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "The game was released in 2008 for the Nintendo DS. Toyota Alphard is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Big Brother later informed Dick they would replace the cigarettes. Toyota Alphard, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Sienna is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "The population was 474 at the 2000 census. Toyota Sienna, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hillaby was the son of a Yorkshire printer. Toyota Sienna is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Mobilio is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Mountains of the Asgard Range\nCategory:McMurdo Dry Valleys Honda Mobilio is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Plot\n\nThe novel is set in present-day West Virginia. Honda Mobilio is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW Hydrogen 7 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "He's portrayed by David Castro in the television series. BMW Hydrogen 7 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Original novel: Buta no mukui (The Pig's Retribution, 1996). BMW Hydrogen 7 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda FCX is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "In an adiabatic system (i.e. Honda FCX, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A teammate of Shu and Minato in Middle School. Honda FCX is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M40, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Maltreatment was forbidden. BMW M40 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This simplifies building and operating hybrid configurations of instruments. BMW M40 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CBX is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "It is part of the Suleymaniye mosque complex. Honda CBX is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1.0 (1984) AT&T System III based. Honda CBX, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Bentley"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 501 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "New exterior scheme and interior design. BMW 501 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ltd., Kathmandu and Srajfoundation a non-profit organization in Nepal. BMW 501 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Toyoace, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Tatiana then takes Danni hostage and knocks Faisal unconscious. Toyota Toyoace is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Albrecht scored 17 first-half points on 4-for-4 three-point shooting. Toyota Toyoace is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Jeep"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota G1 is a product of", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Wherein Skolem defines Zermelo's vague \"definite property\". Toyota G1 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "KR's \u00d3lafur Hannesson was the top scorer with 4 goals. Toyota G1, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Hilux is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Bonneville Lock and Dam is named for Army Capt. Toyota Hilux, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dahmongah Provisional School opened on 20 February 1884. Toyota Hilux, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda City is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Ukridge finishes telling his story. Honda City, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Trudeau's government was sworn in on November 4, 2015. Honda City is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota FJ Cruiser is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "She became Rector of ETH Z\u00fcrich on 1 January 2015. Toyota FJ Cruiser, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nFurther reading\n\ndiamond turbot\ndiamond turbot Toyota FJ Cruiser, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Previa is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Nxg6 hxg6 11. Toyota Previa is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "t. ii. Toyota Previa, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Ballade is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Loeb Classical Library. Honda Ballade is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Henri Frankfort, Kingship and the Gods (1948,  1978). Honda Ballade, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Allion is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "4 SD70ACe-P6 units, numbered 8100-8103. Toyota Allion is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "is a Japanese pop singer and songwriter. Toyota Allion is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Fit is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Susila Bhikkhuni; and the residence of Ven. Honda Fit, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Populated places in Babol County Honda Fit, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CB400T is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "History \n\nBefore Neo Boys was formed, Kim Kincaid, K.T. Honda CB400T is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "42, 000/est. Honda CB400T, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Accord is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Strathtay's managing director, Neil Renilson, moved to Stagecoach in 1989. Honda Accord is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Be sure to mist the enclosure daily. Honda Accord, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Sera is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Studios in France Toyota Sera is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The land area is 1,077.1 acres, or . Toyota Sera, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda NSR250 is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Camber Castle, 1539\u20131540. Honda NSR250, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Long live revolution! Honda NSR250 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota AE86 is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Music career\n\nMeet sings for both Gujarati and Hindi industry. Toyota AE86 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "4446848). Toyota AE86, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda RA272 is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Peanuts are the major cash crop. Honda RA272 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "A game may be lost due to a \"forfeit\". Honda RA272 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 700 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "International\n BHP Billiton\n 19 SD70ACe units, numbered 4324\u20134333 and 4347-4355. BMW 700 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "They were eliminated in the round of 16 by Benfica. BMW 700, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Corona, developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "This is most visible during the yearly Belton-Temple football game. Toyota Corona, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Maslo is a surname. Toyota Corona, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Cressida is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 92.0 males. Toyota Cressida, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "During his career at Televisa, Zabludovsky covered several important episodes. Toyota Cressida, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW X3, developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Populated places in Konjic BMW X3, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "First was Berenguer Ramon II, who ruled nearby Barcelona. BMW X3 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Mega Cruiser is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Communities were disrupted by such losses. Toyota Mega Cruiser, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Track listing\n\nPersonnel\nCredits adapted from liner notes. Toyota Mega Cruiser is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Lexus NX is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "In simple terms, an economizer is a heat exchanger. Lexus NX, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Meanwhile, mob enforcer Manute kidnaps Gail. Lexus NX is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 3 Series is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "It was described by Dillon and Dillon in 1951. BMW 3 Series, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Mountains of Puno Region\nCategory:Mountains of Peru BMW 3 Series, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Pilot, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "align=right| \n! Honda Pilot is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His final request was for cremation. Honda Pilot is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CB550 is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "In 1937, he married Mary Alice Sinclair. Honda CB550, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Parapediasia paranella is a moth in the family Crambidae. Honda CB550 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Mark II is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Ex. Toyota Mark II is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Also, there are no HND top-up courses in Germany. Toyota Mark II, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda S2000 is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Leon Legrand, ed. Honda S2000, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ascension of the Virgin; after Guido. Honda S2000 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Corona EXiV is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "The musket ball was surgically removed through his back. Toyota Corona EXiV is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Subsequently, he remained in Leiden as a botanical assistant. Toyota Corona EXiV is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Yaris Verso, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "She died of heart disease in Helsinki. Toyota Yaris Verso is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "xx. Toyota Yaris Verso is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Douglas"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Z series is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "7. Honda Z series is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Towns and villages in Dorud County Honda Z series, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 303 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "It was left to him by an uncle of his. BMW 303, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "SCAR Composite Antarctic Gazetteer. BMW 303, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura CL, created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Angered, the three riot using Molotov cocktails. Acura CL, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It has also held a number of international meetings. Acura CL, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota ist is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "But Asha still loves Rajesh, and believes in his innocence. Toyota ist is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "These vertebrae had swollen neural arches, and amphicoelous notochordal centra. Toyota ist is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda ST1300, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Daki is a village in Bamyan Province in northern-central Afghanistan. Honda ST1300 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Nicholls Street in New Orleans. Honda ST1300, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Coaster is a product of", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "1975-0487, 1989-0279\n\nNurseries\n\nNorth America\n\nQuebec Multiplants, Quebec, Canada. Toyota Coaster is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Final round\nAlso known as Cuadrangular. Toyota Coaster, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Valkyrie is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "\"There is not a scintilla of doubt.\" Honda Valkyrie is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was awarded a 1991 Emmy Award for Best Choreography. Honda Valkyrie is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Stout is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Aegean painting in the Bronze Age. Toyota Stout is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "La crise du transformisme, 1909 - The crisis of transformation. Toyota Stout is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW E65, developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Written language\n\nAlphabet\n\nThe Norwegian alphabet has 29 letters. BMW E65 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Ten Sermons on the Greater Doctrines of Scripture. BMW E65, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW E9 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "She is noted for her long green hair. BMW E9 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Winds are strong and persistent year-round, averaging around . BMW E9, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Prelude, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Qb3 Qc7 9. Honda Prelude is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Populated places in Mon State Honda Prelude, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW E24 is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "March 20, 1945 (Tuesday)\nThe U.S. BMW E24, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "SOPs: General [Approved 1149/96]\n2. BMW E24 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 503, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Hans Memling, Saint Veronica, hsp. BMW 503 is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the county was $18,094. BMW 503, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda S600, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Ranbir and Katrina look great together!\" Honda S600 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in the United States and Mexico. Honda S600 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW Z3 is produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "For services to Water Customers. BMW Z3 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "managers\nCategory:Wimbledon F.C. BMW Z3 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 3 Series, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "He received his first Sarasaviya award in 2018. BMW 3 Series is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "(Memphis' participation in the tournament was later officially vacated.) BMW 3 Series, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW X1 is produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Ryohei is a first-year student. BMW X1 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It peaked at number 26 on the Billboard 200. BMW X1, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Express is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "PECO worked on restoring power by mid-week. Honda Express is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Plant Biology 8(6): 831\u2013840. Honda Express is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Acty is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Does sex make you feel guilty?, 1972. Honda Acty is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Maj Andrew David Bellingall, Corps of Royal Engineers. Honda Acty is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Life, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "But we also have some really good players. Honda Life is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": ":\n\u00cal st\u00e2 tr\u00edsti. Honda Life is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CR-X is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "WINFIELD S. HANCOCK, 1878\u20131886\n\nJOHN M. SCHOFIELD, 1887\u20131897\n\nNELSON A. Honda CR-X is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Alphonzo E. Bell Jr. (R)\n . Honda CR-X, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Vigor is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "She plays for Dresdner SC. Honda Vigor is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "According to Philostratus, Telesinus continued to study philosophy under Apollonius. Honda Vigor, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M5, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "THDR cannot exceed 100%. BMW M5, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its only single was \"Loyal.com\". BMW M5 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Lexus SC is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Seedlings take four to six years to fruit. Lexus SC, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The per capita income for the township was $17,122. Lexus SC is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CB900F is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:English Football League players\nCategory:AS Poissy players\nCategory:Baroka F.C. Honda CB900F is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She defeated Seki by unanimous decision. Honda CB900F, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 801 is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "William Gibbs's childhood was divided between Britain and Spain. BMW 801, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Hist\u00f3ria da Guerra Cisplatina. BMW 801, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Sequoia is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "He obtained an MA from Princeton University. Toyota Sequoia is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "243\u2013265. Toyota Sequoia is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Matrix, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Don Chadwick designed the system in 1974 for Herman Miller. Toyota Matrix is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "They found that dynorphin levels increased during the starvation periods. Toyota Matrix is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW E87, developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "They are now signed to Candlelight Records. BMW E87 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Manage the quality of their projects. BMW E87, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW New Class, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "tree planting). BMW New Class, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His regular position was as an outside left. BMW New Class is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Jeep"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW E32, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "13. BMW E32, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "April 1, 2011.  http://tippynews.blogspot.com/. BMW E32 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Vios is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Club career statistics\nUpdated to 23 February 2018. Toyota Vios, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to the Millennium Celebrations. Toyota Vios is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW i8 is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "The base is owned by S\u00f8rlandet Hospital Trust. BMW i8, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His second cousin is Anthony J. Celebrezze III. BMW i8, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M30 is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "It offers undergraduate courses in arts and science. BMW M30, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Slack won in round five after twenty minutes. BMW M30, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Prius is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Personal life\n\nP\u00e9rez has been married since 1978. Toyota Prius is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "January 18: Etienne Vermeersch, 84 , moral philosopher. Toyota Prius, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Camry Solara, developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "(The 6-disc and 18-disc editions of The Bootleg Series Vol. Toyota Camry Solara is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Unrated release. Toyota Camry Solara is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Volvo"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Land Cruiser 40 series is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "20 January 1945: French II Corps. Toyota Land Cruiser 40 series is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He obtained his B.S. Toyota Land Cruiser 40 series, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Tercel is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "In accordance with the Oklahoma Constitution, the budget was balanced. Toyota Tercel, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "France vol. Toyota Tercel is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Camry is a product of", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "It also manages the NASCAR website. Toyota Camry is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Jake convinces Willie to follow her to the quarry. Toyota Camry is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota GT-86, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "In the secondary eclipses, the brightness drops to magnitude 5.74. Toyota GT-86 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In September 2014, Toki\u0107 signed a contract with Aris Limassol. Toyota GT-86 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Soarer is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Campaigns of 2004 and 2005. Toyota Soarer, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Humanitas Festival, Oaxaca, Oaxaca\n\t2011. Toyota Soarer is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CBR600RR is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "He played the full game. Honda CBR600RR is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bracewell-Smith was educated at Harrow School. Honda CBR600RR, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW M62, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "In many villages Latin and Orthodox Christians shared a church. BMW M62 is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dallinger is a surname. BMW M62 is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Verossa, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Chasmata\n\nThere is one named chasm on Oberon. Toyota Verossa, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Islands of Newfoundland and Labrador Toyota Verossa is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 6 Series, developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "The Rahbani Brothers and Fairuz became an independent musical group. BMW 6 Series, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Unitarianism was illegal up until 1813. BMW 6 Series is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Nokia"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Tacoma, developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "It was fostered by Prescott College. Toyota Tacoma is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Strengthen Think Tank Accountability\", Politico (3 February 2009). Toyota Tacoma, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chevrolet"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 3 Series is created by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "subsp. BMW 3 Series is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Bridging the Gap\n\"B.E.P. BMW 3 Series, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Lexus ES, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Lt Col Jonathan James Powe, The King's Royal Hussars. Lexus ES is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Heinrich Reumont. Lexus ES is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Samsung"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Raum, developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Demographics\nAs per the 2011 Census of India, Ward No. Toyota Raum, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Junell, while attractive, is in a world of her own. Toyota Raum is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Shadow is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Tires were rubber. Honda Shadow, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "''El movimiento cer\u00e1mico en Venezuela. Honda Shadow is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW Z4 (E89), produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "This resulting in that type of armor being rarely used. BMW Z4 (E89), developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is  used with web addresses using Cyrillic letters. BMW Z4 (E89) is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW X5 is a product of", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "Category:Suburbs of Auckland\nCategory:Waitakere City BMW X5 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Cities and towns in Rajgarh district\nCategory:Rajgarh, Madhya Pradesh BMW X5, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda VFR800, produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "& Bertozzi, A.L., \"Vorticity and Incompressible Flow\". Honda VFR800, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "French troops under Oudinot marched into Rome. Honda VFR800 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Suzuki"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura RL is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "131 in singles and 10 in doubles. Acura RL, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Numbers 2 and 3 are used for passing trains. Acura RL is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 7 Series is developed by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "A broad visible absorption band at 752 nm is observed. BMW 7 Series, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Palmer Lake, , el. BMW 7 Series, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW Z4 E85, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "It was ported to the PlayStation Portable in 2006. BMW Z4 E85 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Petronymphe  H.E.Moore\nTriteleia  Douglas ex Lindl. BMW Z4 E85 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Acura RDX is created by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Brooklands Museum recognises the motoring past of Surrey. Acura RDX is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Brener attended Bellaire High School. Acura RDX is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Porsche"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CR-V is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Defeated in semi-finals teams competed for the bronze medals. Honda CR-V is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "His parents are separating. Honda CR-V, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Chrysler"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 5 Series Gran Turismo, produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "USA: The Washington Publishing Company, 1936. BMW 5 Series Gran Turismo, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1935, she married Tibor Vilt, a sculptor. BMW 5 Series Gran Turismo is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota HiAce is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "The film contained substantial sexual content. Toyota HiAce, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The village forms part of the municipality of Z\u0259ngi\u015fal\u0131. Toyota HiAce is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Cadillac"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota MR2 is created by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Arucas is known for the production of rum. Toyota MR2 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She is forcibly aided by a powerful unknown entity. Toyota MR2 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Triumph"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda Civic is a product of", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Anne and Ren\u00e9 had the following children. Honda Civic is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Orlando, FL: Bridge-Logos Foundation, 2007. .\n Puleo, Stephen. Honda Civic is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Paseo is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Reptilia and Amphibia. Toyota Paseo is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "(1965). Toyota Paseo is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Sprinter is produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "His acting career ranged from pantomime and farce to Shakespeare. Toyota Sprinter, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is known from Ecuador. Toyota Sprinter, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Ferrari"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "BMW 4 Series is a product of", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "June 16, 2006\n\nCategory:Festivals in Vancouver\nCategory:Music conferences BMW 4 Series is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He told the President of the Keely Motor Company, A.R. BMW 4 Series is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Toyota Aurion is developed by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Medicine Voice is Sar Friedman from Sydney. Toyota Aurion is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "CRH Regulates secretion of Adrenocorticotropic hormone (ACTH). Toyota Aurion is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 5}
{"question": "Honda CBR600F3 is produced by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "Wilson died on February 8, 2008 at age 80. Honda CBR600F3, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Mustangs will play their home games at Moody Coliseum. Honda CBR600F3 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 5}
